

PROFILE

I offer 1 year of professional experience in development and 2 additional years of hands on experience on projects from a private university.

Currently I am working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK for J Sainsbury's.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

CONTACT

Phone:

+44 7448719858

Email:

atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian

HOBBIES & SPORTS

Badminton | Football | Chess

LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

ATANAS KAMBITOV

Software Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sainsbury's | Software Engineer | Coventry UK 03/12/2018 - Now (1 year)

Experienced with Microservice architecture and full-stack development including unit, integration and performance testing.

Hands on experience in .Net Core, React, SQL, relational and non-relational databases, Docker, Azure - DevOps, SignalR, Key vaults, AAD, Redis, Container Registry, Kubernetes, App Service, Azure Cosmos Db, Azure Service Bus, Event Hub, Stream analytics, PowerBI, MVC, MVVM, REST, SOAP XML, JSON.

Working in an agile way with scrum in a team of five people providing code quality, latency, stability and performance following solid principles.

SoftUni | Student | Sofia, Bulgaria 05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Hands on experience with backend API's, databases and frontend apps. Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines in a high pressure environment with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Agile Methodologies | Microservice Architecture | Azure | Solid Principles | MVC MVVM | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker | REST API | .NET Core | .Net Framework React.js | Redux | SQL | Angular | Typescript | JavaScript | Mongo DB | JQuery HTML5 & CSS3 | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js & Express.js

EDUCATION

South-West University "Neofit Rilski"

15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years) Bachelor degree in Informatics.

Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

DIPLOMAS & CERTIFICATES

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

Angular

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

React.is

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop